The world today is built on nothing but lies.
And I, Kiyotaro Ichikawa, was born to bring an end to it all.
The holy grounds of this library quell my terrible powers.
It's a placement for me alone.
No outsiders must ever be allowed within.
Ana Yamada.
The prettiest girl in Meguro War and a model.
She's the girl I want to kill most of all.
And...
She's here now, fixing herself up some nero nero nero nay.
Again? Seriously? It's the middle of the day!
Even if it wasn't, aren't you a little old for that?
That's not a junior high sorta choice!
What now?
Oh, right. If I remember, she probably needs water to fill that thing.
Like anyone was gonna steal it!
That's Ana Yamada.
An intruder on these holy grounds of mine.
or like a
Or even...
Or even more.
Can't breathe!
Other waters have next weißeicles that some of us,
have met.
Oh
色に
茜さす日は柔らかに
はぜた
しゃように
僕らは目もわかぬまま
There is.
I'm giving all day long,
and soon my love.
And I'll send you myкт.
See you next time.
Bye.
Shura's taking her a while. How far off did she go?
Oh no.
Huh. Looks like she spilled a little bit.
Off to get more, is she?
Wait. Did she...
She spilled Puddlesworth! How many times has she refilled that thing?
How dare she do this to this holy side of mine? Water is these books' worst enemy!
Th-that was fast.
I was going to wipe up later.
No, uh, it's fine, really.
I'll wipe it up later!
Why doesn't she just get a cup to fill up? Or something?
Guess that would involve going to the home ec room, though.
Only three minutes of recess left.
The home ec room is on the far end of the top floor.
一寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸二寸сят Uneeヾ
And I'm quite lucky now.
That's my oyunstmanas.
keywords
The more you mix na-na-na-na-na-na-na, the more it changes color, and the better it gets.
Wow!
How very refined!
Don't even start!
Take it.
Giving me her trash again?
Keep it!
It's for you!
I...
I don't want it!
Racism is over!
Heading to class!
No, I do want this!
I really freaking do!
Once again, she steals away my precious time in my secret place.
I'm going to have to eliminate her from this world the first chance I get!
Get some death perception, girl!
Are you trying to bruise up your face or something?
You do it for me then!
That's not happening!
Alright!
Well then I guess I'll have to do it!
You're the best, Moeko!
But this will leave me hot too, so...
Let's try this!
Now this is bliss!
Can you please learn some death perception?
Like another scene right out of a Moe manga.
But what I don't understand is...
Why is she always snacking alone if she has so many friends to hang around and eat with?
It doesn't compute!
Give me that paper!
Has she caught on to my murderous intent?
Does she go there alone?
Just to lure me out?
Is she planning to off me at the library?
I'm sweating to death here!
Someone trade shirts with me please!
Summer...
Shirt...
Sweat?
That means...
We might be able to see their bras!
What the hell?
Can this guy read my mind?
Just like we can see your man tits through your sweaty t-shirts, see?
Quit comparing his with hers!
I'm gonna stroll on over there and try and sneak a peek at some juicy titties.
No! You can't!
Don't do this, Adachi!
I'm sending this message straight to your brain!
You've got to stop!
It's no use!
I've got no choice!
Sorry, dude.
Here you go. Not so fast.
Hm?
Hm.
All in order.
Yeah, okay.
Huh?
Where are you going?
Let's stand outside the teacher's room.
We might catch some of the A.C. air leaking out.
Ugh...
Good grief.
Left foot, right foot.
You've got this?
You mind telling me why I gotta do this on such a hot-ass day?
You lost rock, paper, scissors.
Yamada's closest friend is long-suffering Chihiro Kobayashi.
In my head, I always call her Yamada's boyfriend.
Her boyfriend has it rough.
Like how she won't even utter a complaint that she's too heavy.
Goal!
Good effort.
Alright, I'll give you a lift next then. Hop on up, short stack.
No thanks. I prefer not to embarrass myself.
What? You're saying what I just-
But not even her attached-at-the-hip boyfriend...
Yeah, I am!
...comes with her here.
Basically, she's always alone.
She must have caught on to my plan.
Hm?
It...
Hey, can I borrow that?
Hm?
Th...
This?
Yep.
Look at that.
Not even hitting my face.
Ugh...
This is one of those smell-good fans.
No, it isn't.
It is!
See?
Huh?
Ugh...
She's wearing her swimsuit.
Right?
Yeah.
Do we even have swimming today?
Oh, she must be using it to hide her bra.
Still, not bad.
Yeah?
Oh, Michael?
What's up?
Wait.
Now?
Now what?
Ichikawa!
What are you doing?
Sit down!
What?
What's going on?
Have you seen Yamada?
C-c-couldn't say.
She seems mad.
This about the snacks?
I can feel how warm she is.
Oh, no!
I feel a raging boater coming on!
Mm.
Oh.
Hm?
Good grief.
Ugh.
Busted already.
Wait.
She's joining me?
Maybe for the snacks?
Yamada oughta just share.
Whatever.
I'll just let her have some.
Um...
Thanks, but I'm allergic so I can't eat snack food.
Uh-oh.
Sorry.
She's got this weird way of looking out for me.
Once, when she was at my house,
I started getting worried she was in the bathroom for so long.
But she was just chowing down in the hall.
Snack time is a must for her, I guess.
Wait.
Is that why she's always here alone?
She's looking out for her boyfriend?
Though, that's why I like her.
Yeah.
Right.
But if I'm honest,
it's really not fair she gets the good looks and personality.
Always dressed nice and fashionable, too.
Yeah?
Oh.
Not to mention,
she's also super cool when she's modeling.
Right.
Yeah.
You don't say.
Hmm.
Ahem.
See that?
Say something nice and she pops out.
Oh, was that a trick?
You bet.
Yeah, right.
Bet that was all true.
You wish.
Come on.
Piggyback?
Yeah.
Fine, fine.
I get it.
You wanted one from the start, didn't you?
Now I see.
Yeah.
Makes sense.
It all comes together.
Summer break is over, and this weekend, we have the most pointless school event after the sports festival.
The culture festival.
The whole school's in a fuss getting ready for it.
Apparently, our class is doing a haunted house or something.
They're tombstones.
The art club can't handle it all by themselves, so I'm helping out.
Best way to get through stuff like this is to basically fade out of existence.
You have nice handwriting, don't you?
It was you that made the poster for your group in the last presentation, wasn't it?
Um, what?
No.
We need help with the graveyard.
Can you please do it?
I draw every day, but we're talking scary stuff.
Ah, thank you so much.
Um, sure.
Damn it.
Let me just go to the bathroom first.
Okay, sure.
If I'm gonna do this, I might as well do it good.
Hey, you probably want it to look a lot murkier than that.
Oh, true.
And this area here should be a little darker.
Makes sense.
Are those, like, real boobs?
Like this, maybe?
I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
I will never do it again!
Cut!
That's enough!
That was some terrible acting!
Blah!
What is that?
I'll tell you what, sucky!
But it worked.
Ichikawa was super spooked by it.
Right?
No.
I...
Shut up and come with me!
Must be nice to be slim.
Like Yamada, you know?
We've all got our own special something.
Okay.
That should pretty much do it.
I'll go empty the bucket.
Thanks a lot.
Oh, you're done!
Uh...
That's...
My grave.
Hey!
What the hell, man?
What's the big idea?
Uh...
Who wrote that?
What happened?
Crap.
Hara wrote all those.
Does Hara...
I bet Yamada's had plastic surgery.
Wish she'd just die!
Actually hate her.
Did you write that creep?
No, I didn't write that.
Hang on.
If I tell them, the girls are gonna get real mean.
If it wasn't you, then who was it?
No.
Yeah.
It was me.
What happened?
Crap.
Hara wrote all those.
Does Hara...
I bet Yamada's had plastic surgery.
Wish she'd just die.
Actually hate her.
Did you write that creep?
No, I didn't write that.
Hang on.
If I tell them, the girls are gonna get real mean.
No.
Yeah.
It was me.
What's the big idea, huh?
Punk?
It better be good.
Or...
Or you're in for a beating.
Quit using me to try and impress her.
Crap.
I gotta say something.
Well...
Uh...
Just...
Dying's not really a bad thing.
What the hell am I saying?
Death...
Is what...
Saves us.
What the hell am I saying?
What's wrong?
Oh, hey.
They're beefing because Ichikawa wrote Yamada on a tombstone.
What?
No, he didn't.
I wrote that on there.
Huh?
I'm so sorry.
I was just writing down common last names to place on the tombstones.
True.
I see a Kobayashi in there, too.
And Yoshida.
Sorry.
I'll erase them all.
Was that all?
Better be more careful next time.
About what?
Okay, then.
Let's just paint over all of them first.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry.
Yamada!
Let's practice another round!
What...
What just happened?
With the names gone...
Huh?
They just look like regular blocks of Konyaku.
Uh...
Then maybe...
Really?
Sorry?
Sorry...
For what?
What was she apologizing for?
And why?
Uh...
I wonder if I'd be scarier if I was bloody.
Hang on.
If you're going to put some on, you should add more black.
That makes it look eerie.
Or more eerie, actually.
And...
Really layer it on.
That'll make it more realistic.
Oh!
Hmm...
Alright.
There you go.
I thought we had to layer it on.
No, it's even more realistic this way.
Huh?
And so...
The Culture Festival begins.
But this is just junior high.
So it's just another lame event with research exhibits and performances by some of the clubs.
Same as any other day.
Thank you!
I saw the story you posted!
The more social sorts are busy meeting people outside our grade.
We promise we won't!
Thank you!
I might have helped prep.
But come day of, I'm always on my own.
Maybe I'll just coop myself up in the bathroom playing games.
Oh!
You gals on your own?
I know that voice!
It's him!
Senior pick-up artist!
Wanna hang with us?
No!
Um...
We're, uh...
That's it!
Be a good boyfriend and turn him down!
Sounds fun!
Let's go check it out!
You bitch!
Let's get it on!
Where should we go first?
I'm so excited!
Dammit!
He hasn't given up yet!
This is what I hate about those extrovert guys!
Though...
I mean...
I guess he was the first one...
Here goes!
Ready?
To start trying to pull my bike out of the river.
Makes it all the worse when guys like that aren't actually awful.
Yeah, sure are!
But we're on a little bit of a break right now.
Oh, yeah?
Hm?
Say, by the way...
Wait a second...
Are those girls...
In battle formation?
Really?
It's a literal fortress of friendship!
Girls sure know how to look out for each other.
Maybe we all should.
You mean all of us?
Hey!
Ah, shoot!
How am I gonna tail them now?
Must be nice.
You're so lucky.
I know, right?
Alright.
I'll just head in here.
Then...
Make my way through...
And once I get out here...
Wait...
Where did they go?
They couldn't have gone that far.
Oh...
Nothing's coming through!
I broke right through their friendship fortress!
Hey!
Was this one any good?
Uh...
Kinda?
Not that I have a clue.
Oh, look at this!
It's not half bad, huh?
Who are you to be judge?
Uh...
If this is the station, then Morioka's snack shop is right around here.
That's the first place you look for?
Which means...
My house must be over here.
Where's your place at?
Huh?
Uh...
Well...
Maybe around...
Here?
Hmm...
Just a little over a kilometer, I guess.
Huh?
The distance from my house.
The...
Think it's okay to take a picture?
Okay.
Sure.
Wait...
What?
What are you...
How's that?
No!
Uh...
Of the map!
Oh...
Hell yes!
Oh!
Thank you!
Hey!
Can you stop running off like that?
What are you, a cat?
Look, isn't this something?
Yeah.
Cool.
What is it?
Wow!
Is this some countryside map?
You'd think, right?
Over here's where my house is.
Year two, class ones.
Our town, 80 years ago, won this year's top prize.
作詞・作曲・編曲 初音ミク
初音ミク